(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
「hololive 3rd generation live きゅーるるん大作戦」開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Waiting Screen] hololive 3rd Gen Live "Kyururun Grand Strategy" - The concert will be starting soon
注意事項：照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OK
[Attention] Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK
2次販売グッズ：応援セット / 推しマフラータオル
[Merchandise] 2nd Round: Support Set / Fan Muffler Towel
2次販売グッズ：ペンライト / Tシャツ / ペンライトカバー / ランダム缶バッジ
[Merchandise] 2nd Round: Penlight / T-shirt / Penlight Cover / Random Badges
2次販売グッズ：アクリルスタンド / モチーフストラップ / リュック
[Merchandise] 2nd Round: Acrylic Stand / Motif Strap / Backpack
2次販売グッズ：アクリルパネル
[Merchandise] 2nd Round: Acrylic Panel
3期生へのファンお祝いメッセージ
[Fan Messages] Congratulatory Messages to the 3rd Generation Members
ファンによるイラストやメッセージ
[Fan Messages] Fan Artworks & Warm Messages for the Concert
ライブ開催を記念したファンからの応援メッセージ
[Fan Messages] Celebrating the 3rd Generation Live
各メンバーへの温かいメッセージ
[Fan Messages] Heartfelt Support for Each Member
3期生メンバーへの応援メッセージ
[Fan Messages] Support and Love from the Fan Community
ライブに向けてのファンの想い
[Fan Messages] Fan Sentiments and Wishes for the Upcoming Live Show
ファンによるお祝いメッセージ
[Fan Messages] Congratulatory Artwork and Messages from Fans
3期生への愛が詰まったファンメッセージ
[Fan Messages] Fan Messages Filled with Love for the 3rd Generation Members
きみのこと大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you so much
あふれるこの愛きっともっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop anymore
あいあいあいあい♡あいらぶゆー
Ai Ai Ai Ai ♡ I love you
もうあいあいあいあい♡あいにーじゅー
Already Ai Ai Ai Ai ♡ I need you
もっと もっと もっと
More and more and more!
...愛させて！
...let me love you!
ぎゅっとハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My heart leaps up with a tight hug!
雨が降っても あみゃみゃみゃみゃ
Even if it rains, amya-mya-mya-mya!
こんなになってもいいんです 抜け出せない！
It's fine even if it gets like this, I can't escape!
どうしたもんかの ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nui-nui-nui?
助けてきみたち あほーいほい
Help me, everyone, ahoy-hoy!
まった まった まった まった
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
[きめるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドル、推してかないと！～ 開演までしばらくお待ちください]
[Title: Operation Kimerurun - Must Support the Strongest Idols! Please wait a moment for the show to begin]
[Sponsors 協賛]
[Sponsors]
アニメにハマって
I got hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった！
and now I really want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
Singing karaoke while watching
カラオケ歌えるなんて...
scenes of my favorite characters...
尊すぎてツライっ！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Let's find songs we want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
全国のアミューズメント施設にてホロライブ3期生プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes are rolling out at amusement facilities nationwide!
パペットぬいぐるみ (全2種)
Puppet Plushies (2 types in total)
寝そべりミニマスコット —ホロライブ3期生— (全4種)
Nesoberi Mini Mascots - Hololive 3rd Gen (4 types in total)
大判マウスパッド —ホロライブ3期生— (全1種)
Large Mouse Pad - Hololive 3rd Gen (1 type in total)
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね♪ 詳しくはキャラ広場で検索
Get them at amusement facilities nationwide! Search Chara Hiroba for details.
吉野家でごはんでしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya!
ぎゅう。
Beef.
ぎゅう、ぎゅう。
Beef, beef.
ぎゅう。
Beef.
うま！
Delicious!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Savor the seriousness of the original.
牛丼は吉野家。
For beef bowls, it's Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれな。
It has to be this.
ホロライブ3期生ミニCDコレクション
Hololive 3rd Gen Mini CD Collection
＃さるる大作戦 ライブ会場スペシャルキャンペーン
#Saru-Ru-Ru Campaign Live Venue Special Campaign
1回 500円（税込）
500 yen per play (tax included)
2026年1月17日(土)・18日(日)ライブ会場販売！
On sale at the live venue on January 17th and 18th, 2026!
つながるくるくるますこっと
Connecting spin-around mascots
Attention / ご来場のお客様へ
Attention / To All Visitors
2次販売グッズ
Second Batch Merchandise
せーのっ
Ready, set...
はじまるよ！
It's starting!
ホロライブ 3期生ライブ
hololive 3rd Generation Live,
ぎきるん大作戦
Operation Gikirun:
最強アイドル、推ししかないでしょ！
The Ultimate Idols, You Have to Support Us!
にご来場いただき...
Thank you for coming to...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます！
To make sure everyone enjoys the concert to the end, we have a few announcements!
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, and filming during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
The venue is non-smoking. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他の皆の迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です！
Moshing, diving, and throwing objects onto the stage, or any other acts that disrupt the show or trouble others, are strictly prohibited!
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography are in the venue, so the audience seats may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性が...可能性が、ありますので...うわああっ！あらかじめご了承ください！
These videos and photos may be used for promotions... there is a possibility, so... Whoa! Please understand in advance!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、#きゅるるん大作戦Day1 です！
Also, the concert hashtag is #KyururunDaisakusenDay1!
ハッシュタグを使って、たくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
We'd be happy if you used the hashtag to post and build up the excitement!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well then, there is only a little time left before the show starts.
みんなの声を、たくさん聞かせてぺこ！
Let us hear a lot of your voices, peko!
それじゃあ3期生、円陣行くかー！
Alright, 3rd Gen, let's do our huddle!
みんな今からマイクが無くなるので、静かに、静かに...
Everyone, our mics will be turned off now, so be quiet, be quiet...
#きゅるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ～
[Title: Operation Kyururun ~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But To Support Them~]
hololive 3rd Generation Live
兎田ぺこら
[Usada Pekora]
不知火フレア
[Shiranui Flare]
白銀ノエル
[Shirogane Noel]
宝鐘マリン
[Houshou Marine]
#きゅるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ～
[Title: Operation Kyururun ~The Strongest Idols, You Have No Choice But To Support Them~]
I I I I I love you
I I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more!
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want!
3期生ライブいくぺこー！
3rd Gen Live, here we go, peko!
みんなで最高の思い出作ろうね！
Let's make the best memories together!
きゅるるんな毎日 君だらけ
My sparkling days are full of you
どうかしてるわ ねぇ、私
There's something wrong with me, hey
心臓ドキドキになってるって？ ほうほう
You say my heart is pounding? Oh really?
毎日幻覚現れて
Hallucinations appear every day
頭にお花咲いちゃって
With flowers blooming in my head
恋ってやつは非常識ですわ
This thing called love is absurd!
いっそ食べちゃいたい
I'd rather eat you up
フリーズした感情
My frozen feelings
誰もが持ってるお願い
Everyone has a wish
ちゅちゅちゅ萌えーション
Chu, chu, chu, moe-ation
ドドド急上昇
Do-do-do sudden surge!
これが恋ならもう後悔しないわ
If this is love, I won't regret it anymore
だから！
So!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much!
溢れるこの愛は
This overflowing love
きっとずっともっと止まらない
Surely, forever, and even more, won't stop!
I I I I I love you
君が
And you
I I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more!
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want!
揺れるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My swaying heart goes pyon, pyon, pyon!
沼に落ちてあわあわあわ
Falling into the swamp, panicking!
こんなになっても今更抜け出せない
Even if I end up like this, I can't escape now!
どうしたもんかね ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui, nui, nui!
助けて君たち あほーいほい
Help me, everyone! Ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more!
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want!
ふわふわ浮かぶ夢の中
Floating inside a fluffy dream
君の声で目が覚めた
I woke up to your voice
五感全部が君のシグナル
All five senses are signals of you
毎度お騒がせごめん
Sorry for causing a stir every time
きゅんで壊れちゃいそうだ
Feels like my heart will break from the 'kyun'!
恋ってやつは制御不能ですわ
This thing called love is out of control!
いっそ抱きしめて
I'd rather you hug me
壊してもいいよ
It's fine if you break me
誰にも邪魔はさせない
I won't let anyone get in the way!
ピチピチ感情で
With bouncy feelings
キラキラ急展開
Sparkling sudden turn of events!
これが運命ならもう迷わない
If this is destiny, I won't hesitate anymore!
覚悟してね！
Get ready!
君だけが大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
Only you are my love, love, love, love, love!
私のこの愛は
This love of mine
きっとずっともう離さない
Surely, forever, I won't let go!
B B B My baby
B-B-B, my baby
and
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss me
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more!
私だけを見ててね
Please look only at me!
ムシ太郎は泣いちゃうかもね
Mushi-taro might cry
だってそんなのって無いぺこちゃん
But that's not fair, Peko-chan
わかっているよね ダーリン
You know that, right, darling?
いっぱい愛を待ってます
I'm waiting for lots of love
ノエル もっと！ ペコラ もっと！ フレア もっと！ マリン もっと！
Noel, more! Pekora, more! Flare, more! Marine, more!
ホロライブファンタジーを 愛してるー！
I love Hololive Fantasy!
君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you
溢れるこの愛は きっと ずっと 止まらない
This overflowing love will surely, always, never stop
アイ アイ アイ アイ アイラブユー
I-I-I-I-I love you
君が アイ アイ アイ アイ アイニージュー
I-I-I-I-I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
キミだけ愛させて
Let me love only you
ときめくハートが ぴょん ぴょん ぴょん
My fluttering heart goes pyon, pyon, pyon
矢に射抜かれて お手上げ
Shot by an arrow, I surrender
こんなになったら 魔法は解けません
Now that it's come to this, the magic won't wear off
本気になってる ぬい ぬい ぬい
I'm getting serious, nui, nui, nui
いつでもそばで あい ほい
Always by your side, aye-hoy
もっと もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more, more
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want
アイ アイ アイ アイ アイラブユー
I-I-I-I-I love you
アイ アイ アイ アイ アイニージュー
I-I-I-I-I need you
アイ アイ アイ アイ アイラブユー
I-I-I-I-I love you
私たちの愛をもっと
Give us even more of your love
あ、よいしょ！ ピチピチ！ （アホイ！）
Ah, yoisho! Pichi-pichi! (Ahoy!)
ピチピチ！ （アホイ！）
Pichi-pichi! (Ahoy!)
お色気担当のマリンです （ヨーソロー！）
I'm the sexy Marine! (Yousoro!)
踊るアホイに見るアホイ
Dancing Ahoy and watching Ahoy
たまに脱落 君にマリーンラッシュぶっこむ
Sometimes dropping out, plunging into my Marine Rush with you
おどり！
Dance!
うさぎ大明神
Great Rabbit Deity
さぁさ極楽
Now, to paradise
最強女神ぺこら （ぺこら！）
The strongest goddess Pekora (Pekora!)
回る 回る よしよしして
Spinning, spinning, pat my head
ちょっと！よそ見！横取りすんな！
Hey! No looking away! No stealing!
エリートうさぎが
An elite rabbit
大成功のため
for a huge success!
初見コールもいけちゃう？
Can you do the first-time call too?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
実家のような安心感コール
The back-home-like sense of security call
お決まりの ファンサービス 好き あふれちゃう
The usual fan service, love overflowing
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
極めたオタ芸踊る
Dancing perfected wota-gei
新規もいる 古参いる
There are newbies, there are veterans
もはや生きがいなのがグッドじゃん
It's great that it's already a reason to live!
会いたい 推したい
Want to meet, want to support
現場でテンプレート応援 きゅるきゅる ちあ☆ちあ
Full support at the venue, kyuru-kyuru cheer cheer
それそれ エルフそれ！
Sore sore, Elf sore!
褒められて伸びるエルフです
I'm an elf who grows when praised
ひだり！みぎ！
Left! Right!
世界で一番愛してる
I love you most in the world
今ならチャンネル登録なんて無料！
If you subscribe now, it's free!
ジョイジョイ エンジョイ 団長のノエル
Joy-joy, enjoy, Leader Noel
ゆるふわ脳筋 騎士団長
Soft and fluffy muscle-brained Knight Captain
大盾みたい クラブで歌いたい ぎゅーっと！
Like a large shield, want to sing in a club, tightly!
ぎゅーっと！
Tightly!
歌詞より愛をちょうだい
Give me love more than the lyrics
俺たち実質メンバー
We are practically members
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
ハートの振り付けもコピるん
Copying the heart choreography too
可愛いとか 超えて 好き こじらせちゃう
Going beyond cute, making my love complicated
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
来年も愛を集める
Gathering love next year too
エル友も 塩っ子も
Elfriends too, Shiokko too
一味も 野うさぎも
Ichimi too, Nousagi too
もはや全員愛して決定じゃん
Now it's decided that I love everyone!
生きたい のりたい
Want to live, want to ride
現場で全力応援 きゅるきゅる ちあ☆ちあ
Full support at the venue, kyuru-kyuru cheer cheer
みんなの王様
Everyone's king
みんなの歌姫
Everyone's songstress
みんなの団長
Everyone's leader
みんなの船長
Everyone's captain
ラブ＆ピースなときも
Even in times of love and peace
推しがへこんだときでも
Even when your favorite is feeling down
エラーを重ねたい
I want to pile up errors
君と見たい景色があるんだ
There is a view I want to see with you
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
実家のような安心感コール
The back-home-like sense of security call
お決まりの ファンサービス 大好き 一生好きだよ
The usual fan service, I love you, I will love you forever
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
ラストまで全力で駆け抜ける
Running through with all our might until the end
残念な時も 存在が最強
Even in disappointing times, your existence is the strongest
大優勝！
Grand victory!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
永遠の愛誓える
I can swear eternal love
他推しいる？ 箱推しは？
Do you support others? Are you an all-member fan?
もはや生涯オタオタ決定じゃん
Now it's decided that you are a wota for life!
もっと ずっと もっと ずっと
More, always, more, always
現場で限界応援 きゅるきゅる
Extreme support at the venue, kyuru-kyuru
ちあ！ちあ！
Cheer! Cheer!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's resonate our newborn excitement!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best times and the best friends,
キラメキに乗って☆
let's ride the sparkle! ☆
一生現場で、ちあ！
Forever at the venue, cheer!
ふぅ... はぁ...
*Panting*
みんなー！
Everyone!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ちょっと、ちょっとダンスしすぎた...
Wait, we danced way too much...
落ち着こう、落ち着こう。
Let's calm down, calm down.
落ち着くために自己紹介しよう！
Let's do self-introductions to calm down!
自己紹介オッケー！
Self-introductions, okay!
そうだね！
That's right!
じゃあ、ぺこらから行きますよ！
Then Pekora will go first!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
ホロライブ3期生の、兎田ぺこらと...
Of Hololive 3rd Gen, Usada Pekora and...
お前、「こんぺこ」って言わせてよ！
Hey, let us say "Konpeko"!
言いたかったのに！
I wanted to say it!
もう一回やってよ！もう一回！
Do it again! Do it again!
なんて言えばいいの、ぺこらはじゃあ？
Then what should Pekora say?
「こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー」って言ったら、向こうも言いたいんだよ！
When you say "Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko," they want to say it too!
あ、そういうことね！
Ah, I see!
みんなやってくれますかー？
Will everyone do it?
じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
こんぺこー！
Konpeko!
いいじゃーん！
Nice!
ホロライブ3期生の、兎田ぺこらと...
Of Hololive 3rd Gen, Usada Pekora...
はい、じゃあフレアは「こんぬい」じゃなくて、「はいだーりん」って言うから、「はいはにー」って返してください！
Okay, Flare won't say "Kon-nui", but instead "Hi, Darling", so please reply with "Hi, Honey"!
あー！
Ah!
はい、だーりん！
Hi, Darling!
はい、はにー！
Hi, Honey!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生の、不知火フレアと...
Of Hololive 3rd Gen, Shiranui Flare...
じゃあ、団長は「牛丼は？」って言うんで、「なみもりー！」って言ってください！
Then Danchou will ask "Gyudon is?", so please say "Nami mori!" (Regular size!)
なみもり？ なみもり？ なみもりって何だよ！
Nami mori? Nami mori? What is Nami mori?!
じゃあ、行くよー！
Alright, here we go!
牛丼はーー？
Gyudon isー?
なみもりーー！
Nami moriー!
そう、そうだよねー！
Yes, that's right!
ホロライブ3期生の、白銀ノエルと...
Of Hololive 3rd Gen, Shirogane Noel and...
キミたち！ 今、もしかしてフレアのこと「はにー」って言った？
You guys! Did you just call Flare "Honey"?
言ったよ、お前！
You said it!
よろよろ...
*Wobbling...*
何言ってんの？
What are you talking about?
団長のこと忘れてしまって...
Did you forget about Danchou...?
なんちゃって！
Just kidding!
じゃあ、普通に「あほーい」で行きますんで、「あほーい」って言ってください！
Then I'll go with "Ahoy" normally, so please say "Ahoy"!
はーい！
Okay!
あほーい！
Ahoy!
誰がアホや！
Who are you calling an idiot?!
なんちゃって！
Just kidding!
ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の、宝鐘マリンです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine-desu!
ということで...
So anyway...
みんな、なんかアイドル口上みたいなの募集したやつ、やる？やる？
Should we do those idol calls we gathered? Shall we?
やろう！やろう！
Let's do it! Let's do it!
じゃあ、順番で！
Then, in order!
順番で行きましょう、順番で！
Let's go in order, in order!
みんな覚えてるよね？ぺこらの口上！
Everyone remembers Pekora's call, right?
絶対覚えてないぞ！
They definitely don't!
覚えてるよね？
You remember, right?
覚えてる人、手あげて！
Raise your hands if you remember!
あ、そこそこ...
Ah, some over there...
全然あがってない！
Almost no hands are up!
全然覚えてないって！
They don't remember at all!
じゃあ今から覚えてくださいね！じゃあぺこらから行きますよ！
Then please memorize it now! Alright, Pekora will go first!
ラビット キャロット キラッと登場！最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこ！
Rabbit, carrot, sparkling entrance! The strongest idol Pekora has arrived-peko!
まだまだ続くよ、ぺこらストーリー！
It's still going, the Pekora story!
ちょっと、フレア、めっちゃ難しいんだけどさ、いけるかな、これ？
Wait, Flare's is super difficult, can they do it?
いける、いける！
They can do it!
みんな掛け声いけるよ！
Everyone can do the call!
これ、みんなにもコール＆レスポンスしてほしくて、
I want everyone to do a call and response for this,
「準備は？」って言ったら「万端！」、
so if I say "Are you ready?", say "All set!",
「コールは？」って聞くので「簡単！」って言ってください！
I'll ask "The call?", so please say "Simple!"
手拍子「パンパン！」
Clap your hands, "Clap, clap!"
ステップ「トントン！」
Step, "Tap, tap!"
私は「ふーたん！」
I am "Fu-tan!"
めっちゃ難しい！
That's super hard!
これ練習ね！
This is a practice run!
覚えてください！
Please memorize it!
では、いきますよ！
Alright, here we go!
こんぬい！
Kon-nui!
準備はーー？
Are you readyー?
万端ーー！
All setー!
コールはーー？
The call isー?
簡単ーー！
Simpleー!
手拍子ーー！
Clap your handsー!
パンパンーー！
Clap, clapー!
ステップーー！
Stepー!
トントンーー！
Tap, tapー!
私はーー？
I amー?
ふーたんーー！
Fu-tanー!
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Shiranui Flare-desu!
おおー！すごーい！
Ooh! Amazing!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
じゃあ、次はノエル！
Alright, next is Noel!
ノエル行きます！
Noel is going!
団長、コール＆レスポンスないから、ちょっとラップします！
Danchou doesn't have a call & response, so I'll do a quick rap!
ラップ？！
Rap?!
ここから行こうかな！
Let's start from here!
行きます！
Here I go!
みんなに質問、最高の食べ物！
Question to everyone, what is the best food?
答えは牛丼、おろしは飲み物！
The answer is gyudon, with grated radish it's a drink!
みんなの胸きゅん、ダメダメ重婚！
Everyone's heart-throbbing, no-no bigamy!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエル！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel!
はい、じゃあマリン！
Alright, next is Marine!
え、マリンはコールレスなんで、先に予習しましょうか？
Since Marine has a call-and-response, should we practice it first?
え、マリンが「マリンはー！」って言ったら、君たちは「船長！」で、
When Marine says "Marine is-", you guys say "Captain!", okay?
「船長！」ね。君らは？「一味！」
"Captain!" right. "And you guys are?" "Crewmates!"
一味！一味！
Crewmates! Crewmates!
我ら無敵の？「海賊団！」海賊団！
"Our invincible?" "Pirate crew!" Pirate crew!
で、最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！」って言うから、そしたら問答無用で「可愛い！」って言う。分かりましたね？
And finally, I will say "Houshou Pirate Captain, Houshou Marine!" and then, no questions asked, say "Cute!" Got it?
まあ余裕だよね。素晴らしいお返事できて、丸。
Well, that's easy. You replied wonderfully, gold star.
じゃあ、いきますよ！マリンはー？
Alright, here we go! Marine is-?
「船長ー！」
"Captain-!"
君らはー？
You guys are-?
「一味ー！」
"Crewmates-!"
我ら無敵の？
Our invincible-?
「海賊団！」
"Pirate crew!"
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンですー！
Houshou Pirate Captain, Houshou Marine-!
「可愛いー！」
"Cute-!"
いや、気持ちいい、これ。そんな可愛い？
Wow, this feels so good. Am I really that cute?
よかったね、可愛いって言われて、よかったね。
I'm glad for you. It's nice to be called cute, isn't it?
そんなことないけど。
Not really, though...
え、でもコールアンドレスポンスね、ちょっと一発目から、もう凄い難しいのやらせちゃって、どうもすみませんね。
But seriously, I'm sorry for making you do such a difficult call-and-response right off the bat.
ね、たくさんちょっとね、ありがとう。ありがとう！
Yeah, there was quite a lot. Thank you. Thank you!
ええ、声が聞こえますよ。届きまして。
Yes, we can hear your voices. They reached us.
さっきのさ、うちらの円陣、聞こえました？
By the way, did you hear our huddle earlier?
あ、聞こえた？聞こえた？
Ah, you heard it? You heard it?
やったー！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so glad!
ちょっと、なんか聞こえるかなって不安だったから。
I was a bit worried if you would be able to hear it.
こっちにはね、君らの声、よく聞こえるんだけど。
On our end, we can hear your voices really well.
さすがにマイク通さないと、ちっちゃかったかなと思って。
But we thought it might be too quiet since it wasn't through a mic.
でもお腹から出したからね、お腹から。
But we yelled from our stomachs, from our stomachs.
あ、聞こえた！ありがとう！聞こえるよ！
Ah, they heard it! Thank you! We can hear you!
こっちにも声、聞こえてますよ。あ、衣装のことも言わなきゃ！
We can hear your voices over here too. Ah, we also have to talk about our outfits!
そうだよ！どうですか？
That's right! How do you like them?
突然の新衣装！可愛いでしょ？ちょっとずつ違うところがありますんで。
A sudden new outfit reveal! They're cute, right? There are some parts that are slightly different.
ぺこらは、耳に...
For Pekora, on her ears...
輪っかがついているぺこです！
...there is a ring attached, peko!
なんと発案者はノエちゃん！
And the one who came up with it is actually Noel-chan!
そう、ノエル！凄いでしょ？
Yes, Noel! Amazing, right?
可愛い！
So cute!
マリンはね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほら、こんな感じで、バツバツバツバツ...
For Marine, look, the headdress is like this with crosses...
ハート型になってる！可愛いー！
And it's heart-shaped! "Cute-!"
ノエちゃんは、なんかポンポンついてます。
Noe-chan has pom-poms on her.
なんかポンポンついてる。
Some pom-poms are attached.
フレアは、この頭のリボンかな？
For Flare, is it this ribbon on her head?
可愛いね。あとソックス違います、みんな。隠した。
Cute. Also, our socks are different, everyone. Hidden.
そう、フレアはギャルじゃないんでね。
Yeah, since Flare isn't a gyaru.
私らはギャル！
We are gyarus!
ぺこらもギャル！
Pekora is a gyaru too!
ギャル！ギャルです！
Gyaru! We're gyarus!
ちなみに...
By the way...
何？
What?
みなさん、あの、うちらね、結構めちゃめちゃ喋りすぎてるみたいで。
Everyone, apparently we're talking way too much.
嘘でしょ？！このまま音楽しないのかい？みたいな。
You're kidding?! Like, "Are they not going to play music at this rate?"
あ、そうだよね。
Ah, that's right.
スタッフさんから言われてますけれども、でも、あの、ちなみに配信で見てる方、
We're being told that by the staff, but, by the way, those watching on the stream...
YouTubeで見てる方、あの、概要欄にね、配信チケットのリンクありますので、ぜひ！
...or on YouTube, there's a link to the stream tickets in the description, so please check it out!
次の曲でちょっとチラ見せは...
With the next song, the sneak peek will...
あ、そうだ、終わりぺこなの。終わっちゃうので、今のうちに！
Ah, that's right, it's the end of the free section, peko. It's ending, so do it now!
まだ見、見たい、見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるので、ぜひとも！
There are still many parts we want you to see, so please!
お願いします！
Please!
ハッシュタグ「#つながるホロライブ大作戦Day1」でいっぱい呟いてね！
Please tweet a lot with the hashtag "#tsunagaru_hololive_Day1"!
呟いてください！お願いします！っていうか、そう、これやらないと！
Please tweet it! Thank you! Anyway, yes, we have to do this!
あのね、あのね、生バンドがね、凄いカッコいいじゃない？
You know, the live band is super cool, right?
そう、そうだね。
Yeah, that's right.
だから、ちょっと聴かせたくて。
So, we wanted you to hear them a bit.
じゃあ、ぺこらちゃんから言ってもらっていいですか？
Then, Pekora-chan, could you call them out?
了解！
Roger!
え、バンドキーボード担当、兎田ぺこら！
Uh, on keyboards... Usada Pekora!
おお！凄い！カッコいい！
Oh! Awesome! Cool!
いくよ、ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Here we go! Guitar, Houshou Marine!
おおー！カッコいい！
Oh-! So cool!
はい、え、ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Yes, uh, drums, Shirogane Noel!
ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Dododododo! Amazing!
じゃあ、フレア、ベースやります！
Then, Flare will do bass!
おおー！カッコいい！カッコいい！
Oh-! So cool! Cool!
なんかカッコいいわー。最高！
That's so cool. The best!
サンキュー！はい、うちらが演奏してまーす。
Thank you! Yes, we are the ones performing!
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲、いきましょうか！
Ah, then shall we move on to the next song soon!
あ、場所！場所場所！
Ah, positions! Positions!
あ、こっちじゃない、ここ、ここ。
Ah, not here, here, here.
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲、いきましょう！
Alright, let's head to the next song!
せーの！「リアル・キープ・ファンタジー！」
Ready, set... "Real Keep Fantasy!"
Ｈ-Ｏ-Ｌ-Ｏ-Ｌ-Ｉ-Ｖ-Ｅ
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E
Ｆ-Ａ-Ｎ-Ｔ-Ａ-Ｓ-Ｙ
F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Now!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Now!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
冒険！出発！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Now!
挑戦！開始！さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
お宝探しに
To search for treasure,
大海原
on the vast ocean,
いざ出航だ！
let's set sail!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Off we go! Now, the challenge begins!
耳元からもぴょんぴょん　わくわく　頂点　上昇
Even your ears are hopping, excitingly rising to the top!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Off we go! Now, the challenge begins!
水平線 向こうから 新天地 待っててね
Beyond the horizon, a new world... please wait for us!
運命なんか飛び越してその先へ
Jump over destiny and head beyond that!
さあ！リアリティ ファンタジー 二つの狭間で
Now! Reality and fantasy, between these two worlds,
夢歌え 声高く 一緒に さあ！
sing your dreams, raise your voice, together now!
まだ見ぬ世界へと君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you to a world we have yet to see!
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
A story connecting everyone is about to begin!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Off we go! Now, the challenge begins!
みんなの志 抱き いざ行こう 騎士団 集合！
Holding everyone's ambition, let's go! Order of Knights, assemble!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Off we go! Now, the challenge begins!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切って さらに輝け
With the sun in my heart, cutting through the wind, shine even brighter!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Off we go! Now, the challenge begins!
迷いと夢 晴天に掲げたら 突撃だ
If we raise our doubts and dreams to the clear blue sky, it's time to charge!
よって立つ この旅 見守って
Please watch over this journey that we stand upon!
さあ！リアリティ ファンタジー 二つの狭間で
Now! Reality and fantasy, between these two worlds,
声上げて 向かえユートピアへ さあ！
raise your voice and head towards Utopia, come on!
それぞれの世界から 垣根を越えたら
Once we cross the boundaries of our respective worlds,
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
a story connecting everyone is about to begin!
明るく陽気に荒波乗り越え ホロライブ！
Cheerfully and brightly overcoming the rough waves, Hololive!
愛嬌開放うさ耳澄まして ホロライブ！
Releasing charm, pricking up my rabbit ears, Hololive!
騎士道と誇り胸に刻んだら ホロライブ！
Engraving chivalry and pride in my heart, Hololive!
神話に伝わる神秘な囁き ホロライブ！
The mysterious whisper handed down in myths, Hololive!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Off we go! Now, the challenge begins!
さあ！リアリティ ファンタジー 二つの狭間で
Now! Reality and fantasy, between these two worlds,
夢歌え 声高く 一緒に さあ！
sing your dreams, raise your voice, together now!
まだ見ぬ世界へと君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you to a world we have yet to see!
準備はほらできたよ
Look, the preparations are all done,
ルートの先 決まったよ
and the route ahead is decided!
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
A story connecting everyone is about to begin!
時は2026年！
The year is 2026!
2回目の3期生ライブ！
The second 3rd-generation live concert!
このチャンスを逃してなるものか！
There's no way I'll let this chance slip away!
今こそ！
Now is the time!
全人類兎化計画を...
To carry out...
遂行する！
...the Operation Usagify All Humanity!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peak part of the show has ended! Thank you for watching!